// Veiled modifiers
description
    1 veiled_mod_type
    20
        1 "<veiled prefix Veiled (prefix)>"
        2 "<veiled suffix of the Veil (suffix)>"
        3 "<veiled prefix Leo's Veiled (prefix)>"
        4 "<veiled prefix Catarina's Veiled (prefix)>"
        5 "<veiled prefix Elreon's Veiled (prefix)>"
        6 "<veiled prefix Vorici's Veiled (prefix)>"
        7 "<veiled prefix Haku's Veiled (prefix)>"
        8 "<veiled prefix Tora's Veiled (prefix)>"
        9 "<veiled prefix Vagan's Veiled (prefix)>"
        10 "<veiled prefix Guff's Veiled (prefix)>"
        11 "<veiled prefix It That Fled's Veiled (prefix)>"
        12 "<veiled prefix Gravicius' Veiled (prefix)>"
        13 "<veiled prefix Korell's Veiled (prefix)>"
        14 "<veiled prefix Rin's Veiled (prefix)>"
        15 "<veiled suffix of Janus' Veil (suffix)>"
        16 "<veiled suffix of Hillock's Veil (suffix)>"
        17 "<veiled suffix of Jorgin's Veil (suffix)>"
        18 "<veiled suffix of Cameria's Veil (suffix)>"
        19 "<veiled suffix of Aisling's Veil (suffix)>"
        20 "<veiled suffix of Riker's Veil (suffix)>"

// Fishing lure type
description
    1 fishing_lure_type
    1
        1|# "&lt;Rhoa Feather Lure&nbsp;&bull; Siren Worm Lure&nbsp;&bull; Totemic Wood Lure&nbsp;&bull; Thaumaturgical Lure&gt;"

// Fishing hook type
description
    1 fishing_hook_type
    1
        1|# "&lt;Karui Stone Hook&nbsp;&bull; Ezomyte Shell Hook&nbsp;&bull; Vaal Soul Hook&nbsp;&bull; Eternal Iron Hook&gt;"
